NAING MIN KHANT

Junior Web Developer

PERSONAL DETAILS

No (949), Thayae Khit Tayar St, South Okkalapa Township Yangon

tharkhant777@gmail.com, 09-952 128 314

Date of birth: February 16, 2002

Gender: Male

Nationality: Burmese Website: nmk.netlify.app

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/naing-min-khant

GitHub: github.com/naingminkhant16

EDUCATION

Second Year (Computer Science)

University Of Computer Studies,, Taunggyi

Certificate Of Completion In Basic Web Development

AIMT, Yangon

Certificate Of Completion In Web Application

Development

MMSIT, Yangon

EMPLOYMENT

Internship Junior Developer At Creative Coder Myanmar

Creative Coder Myanmar, Yangon

Jul 2022 - Sep 2022

Dec 2018 - Feb 2020

Nov 2021 - Dec 2021

Mar 2022 - Aug 2022

SKILLS

Web Development in HTML CSS & JavaScript

Programming Languages - PHP & JavaScript

Frameworks - Laravel & VueJS

UI Tools -Bootstrap & Tailwind

PROFILE

Travelling

Web Developer with +1 year experience in PHP, Laravel and various Web Development tools. Thorough knowledge of developing Frontend, Backend, and API. Willingness to learn new things. Love to solve problems. Able to finish the tasks before deadline.